tinkerfcu.org 2006-10-05

# Disclaimer and Privacy Policy

**Disclaimer**

Website Privacy Policy

Member Privacy Policy

Disclaimer and Privacy Statement  

****  
****_  
_ Each member account federally insured to $100,000 by the National Credit Union Administration _  
__  
_ Copyright ©2006 Tinker Federal Credit Union  

| 

The information and materials contained in these pages, and the terms, conditions, and descriptions that appear, are subject to change without notice. Copyright in the pages and in the screens displaying the pages, and in the information and materials therein and in their arrangement, is owned by Tinker Federal Credit Union, unless otherwise indicated. No one has permission to copy or republish any information found on this Web site and any pages thereof, unless otherwise indicated.  Information from this Web site is invalid unless it is read and is presented in its entirety.

TFCU is committed to protecting the privacy of its members and other users of its Web site. We have adopted the following privacy policy for your protection:

**General Web Site Pages**  
TFCU collects and stores information on the domain you use to access its Web site, the Internet address of the site from which you linked directly to our site, and the date and time of your visit to our site. This information is used to measure the number of visitors to the various pages on the site, to help TFCU make improvements to the information contained on the site, and to better serve our members through special marketing and service programs.

**Applications**  
Only business related information is requested on any TFCU online application. This information is used only for review of qualifications for the loan, account, or service for which you are applying. Any information gathered during member application is not given or sold to third parties.

**Online Mortgage Applications**  
All customer information is encrypted using Secured Socket Layer (SSL) technology supported with digital certificates provided by GeoTrust, Inc and requires a browser that supports 128-bit encryption. Applicants will need an Internet Explorer browser (Version 5.0 or greater) or Netscape Navigator browser (Version 6.0 or greater) to receive disclosures electronically. Access to a printer or the ability to download information in order to keep copies for personal records is necessary

**Home Branch, e-Statements and Check Images**  
Personal identifying information, excluding passwords, is collected when a member logs on to Home Branch. This information enables TFCU to regulate entry and to measure member usage. Any personal identifying information gathered during member registration is not sold to third parties. Home Branch is a secured site and requires a browser that supports 128-bit encryption. Macintosh computer users must use Mac OS X 10.1.x or Mac OS X 10.2.x or later, have at minimum a PowerPC 604e 266 MHz (Recommended: PowerPC G4 667MHz or greater), G3, G4, 64 MB RAM (Recommended: 256 MB RAM or greater), 72 MB hard drive space, using Mozilla Firefox 1.04 web browser available free. e-Statements & check images also require Macromedia Flash Player.

**e-mail**  
Personal information contained in e-mail sent by members and non-members may be used by TFCU staff to answer questions, to follow up on suggestions or complaints, or to improve the level of service TFCU provides. Please be advised that e-mail may not be secure against interception by unauthorized individuals. Therefore, if you wish to communicate sensitive or personal information, you may want to use our Web Chat feature or send your message by postal mail.

**Cookies**  
We make use of cookies to track usage and compile statistics about our Web site and Home Branch, and during a Home Branch session to uniquely identify your information. Cookies are small files that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser. In the future, cookies may be used to allow members to set preferences and personalize our Web site. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) However, a cookie is required in order to use Home Branch.

If you have any questions about TFCU's Web site privacy policy, e-mail [comments@tinkerfcu.org](mailto:comments@tinkerfcu.org).

**Notice of Your Financial Privacy Rights** ** _  
_** This is our privacy notice for our members. When we use the words "you" and "your" we mean the following types of members:  

| • | All of our consumer members who have a continuing relationship with us, such as:  
---|---  
• | Savings account  
• | Loan account  
• | Credit card  
• | Safe deposit box  
• | All IRA accounts for which we act as custodian  
  
We will tell you the sources for nonpublic personal information we collect on our members. We will tell you what measures we take to secure that information.

We first define some terms.

**We** , **our** , and **us** means Tinker Federal Credit Union.

**Nonpublic personal information** means information about you that we collect in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. Nonpublic personal information does not include information that is available from public sources, such as telephone directories or government records.

An **affiliate** is a company we own or control.

A **nonaffiliated third party** is a company that is not an affiliate of ours.

 **The Information That We Collect** ** _  
_** We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources: • | Information we receive from you on applications or other forms  
---|---  
• | Information about your transactions with us  
• | Information about your transactions with nonaffiliated third parties  
• | Information from a consumer reporting agency  

**The Confidentiality, Security, and Integrity of Your Nonpublic Personal Information** ** _  
_** We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information. **Nonpublic Personal Information and Affiliates** ** _  
_** We may disclose nonpublic personal information about you. Here are the kinds of nonpublic personal information we may disclose to our affiliates:

Transaction and experience information from our account records:

• | Information about your transactions and experience with us, such as  
---|---  
• | Name  
• | Address  
• | Account number  
  
Federal law allows us to disclose the information listed above with our affiliates. You do not have a right to opt out of the disclosure of this information.

**Types of Affiliates  
**We may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to the following types of affiliates:

• | Financial service providers, such as  
---|---  
• | Securities broker-dealers  
• | Insurance agents  
  
**Reasons For Disclosure**  
Here is why we may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to our affiliates: • | To provide our members with information about additional products and services  
---|---  
**Nonpublic Personal Information and Nonaffiliated Third Parties  
**  
Since we value our member relationship with you, we will not disclose your nonpublic personal information to nonaffiliated third parties, except as permitted by law. This might include disclosures necessary to service your account, perform joint marketing or prevent unauthorized transactions. **Nonpublic Personal Information and Former Members  
**  
We do not disclose nonpublic personal information about former members, except as permitted by law. **Authorized Sharing Outside Marketing Services**  
  
We may disclose the following information to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf: • | Nonpublic personal information we receive from you on an application or other forms, such as  
---|---  
• | Name  
• | Address  
• | Nonpublic personal information about your transactions with us, such as  
• | Types of accounts  
• | Credit card usage  
  
Federal law allows us to disclose the information listed above with companies that perform marketing services on our behalf. You do not have a right to opt out of the disclosure of this information. We may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties as permitted by law.

**Types of Businesses  
**Here are the types of businesses with whom we may disclose nonpublic personal information for outside marketing purposes:

• | Service providers that perform marketing services for us  
---|---  
• | Direct sales companies  
  
**Reasons For Disclosing**  
Here is why we may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf: • | To provide our members with information about additional products and services  
---|---  
  
**Limitations on Disclosure**  
Here are the limitations we impose on the use of nonpublic personal information disclosed to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf: • | We only allow direct mail solicitations.  
---|---  
**Authorized Sharing - Joint Marketing**

We may disclose the following information to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements:

• | Nonpublic personal information we receive from you on an application or other forms, such as  
---|---  
• | Name  
• | Address  
  
Federal law allows us to disclose the information listed above with other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. You do not have a right to opt out of the disclosure of this information. We may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties as permitted by law.

**State Limitations**  
AL, AK, ID, ND and VT — We will not share this information about members who reside in Alabama, Alaska, Idaho, North Dakota or Vermont.  
MA, MS and NJ — We will not share any information derived from share relationships with us about members who reside in Massachusetts, Mississippi or New Jersey.

**Types of Businesses.  
**Here are the types of businesses with whom we may disclose nonpublic personal information under this section

• | Financial service providers, such as  
---|---  
• | Insurance agents  
  
**Reasons For Disclosing**  
Here is why we may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements: • | To provide our members with information about additional products and services  
---|---  

**Transaction Receipts** ****You understand that certain receipts for transactions may contain nonpublic personal information about your account. If you authorize a person who is not on your account to transact business on your account, you authorize us to provide such person with any information that would be given to you as a result of whatever business they transact on your behalf.
